{
    "id": "d253ab10c72740b4a429a57ee8565f6a",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It …………………… for the past month.",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with the time expressions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't rain",
                "hasn't rained",
                "was not raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0cf0089d70af44a0abb37690841254ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Fossil fuels ………………………… coal and petrol are harmful to the environment.",
            "description": "We use such as to give examples.",
            "answers": [
                "such as",
                "like",
                "for example"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d241c3cfbf37420b87f678d5a54c6d5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ....................... is sitting in that corner is my neighbor’s daughter.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c8bc65edfbe4b7baa33bbf3db53cb0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. pay for that drink.",
            "description": "When need is a modal auxiliary verb, questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "don't need",
                "need not",
                "need not to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5726cef500284ca2b9b46711ef1358fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ......................... get a second opinion.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice. ",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better",
                "had better to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f931c357a754a4aafa74bb4e003a0bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of these answers …………………………… correct.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after none.",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d560ee6732f40a99e9834a2822e6e36"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ………………………. friends.",
            "description": "Not any means the same as no.",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "any",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6feaaf6f16fa4519a392ba5aab6dafb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. was there to rescue him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Nobody",
                "Anybody",
                "Noone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "471f060a8b2749b6abad37c0713ec9dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "That wasn’t ………………………… right.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quiet",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24c469cb4b874229aa8dafd73a166eaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… fire, call",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In case",
                "If",
                "In case of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb0ea96fb9dd4e1285edfeefb395b071"
        },
        {
            "question": "Things are getting …………………..",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "worser",
                "worse"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ce634441fa0e419694a1b1d27f3ca518"
        },
        {
            "question": "We lost the deal ………………………….. your obstinacy.",
            "description": "Because of is a preposition. It is followed by a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d672190f7f04e36a08b09a247be1928"
        }
    ]
}